module.exports = {
    question:[{'answer': 'G2',
    'options': [{'description': 'T1 ', 'label': 'T1', 'value': 'T1 '},
     {'description': 'G2', 'label': 'G2', 'value': 'G2'},
     {'description': 'FNC', 'label': 'FNC', 'value': 'FNC'}],
    'question': 'FPX电子竞技俱乐部S9英雄联盟全球总决赛夺冠时对战的队伍是？\nWho was the team that FPX e-sports club S9 League of Legends played against when they won the global finals?'},
   {'answer': '3:00',
    'options': [{'description': '3:00', 'label': '3：0', 'value': '3:00'},
     {'description': '3:01', 'label': '3：1', 'value': '3:01'},
     {'description': '3:02', 'label': '3：2', 'value': '3:02'}],
    'question': 'FPX电子竞技俱乐部S9英雄联盟全球总决赛以多少比分获得胜利？\nBy what score did the FPX eSports Club S9 League of Legends global finals win?'},
   {'answer': 'FPX.Lwx',
    'options': [{'description': 'FPX.xiaolaohu',
      'label': 'FPX.xiaolaohu',
      'value': 'FPX.xiaolaohu'},
     {'description': 'FPX.Care', 'label': 'FPX.Care', 'value': 'FPX.Care'},
     {'description': 'FPX.Lwx', 'label': 'FPX.Lwx', 'value': 'FPX.Lwx'}],
    'question': 'FPX哪位选手创造了英雄联盟全球总决赛0死亡的记录？\nWhich FPX player created the record of 0 deaths in the League of Legends World Finals?'},
   {'answer': 'Paris',
    'options': [{'description': 'Berlin', 'label': '柏林', 'value': 'Berlin'},
     {'description': 'Madrid', 'label': '马德里', 'value': 'Madrid'},
     {'description': 'Paris', 'label': '巴黎', 'value': 'Paris'}],
    'question': 'FPX S9英雄联盟全球总决赛是在哪个城市夺冠？从此粉丝们自称是该城市的市民？\nIn which city did the FPX S9 League of Legends World Finals win? Since then fans have claimed to be citizens of the city?'},
   {'answer': '2years',
    'options': [{'description': '5years', 'label': '五年', 'value': '5years'},
     {'description': '8years', 'label': '八年', 'value': '8years'},
     {'description': '2years', 'label': '两年', 'value': '2years'}],
    'question': 'FPX电子竞技俱乐部成立了几年即获得了一举夺得了世界冠军？\nHow many years has the FPX e-sports club been established and won the world championship in one fell swoop?'},
   {'answer': '2019',
    'options': [{'description': '2018', 'label': '2018', 'value': '2018'},
     {'description': '2019', 'label': '2019', 'value': '2019'},
     {'description': '2020', 'label': '2020', 'value': '2020'}],
    'question': 'FPX电子竞技俱乐部在哪一年入围全球知名Esports Awards年度最佳电竞战队？\nHow many years has the FPX e-sports club been established and won the world championship in one fell swoop?'},
   {'answer': 'Super hero',
    'options': [{'description': 'Kungfu Shaolin ',
      'label': '少林功夫',
      'value': 'Kungfu Shaolin '},
     {'description': 'Super hero', 'label': '超级英雄', 'value': 'Super hero'},
     {'description': 'Avatar', 'label': '天神下凡', 'value': 'Avatar'}],
    'question': 'FPX英雄联盟分部S9英雄联盟全球总决赛冠军皮肤主题是什么？\nWhat is the theme of the FPX League of Legends Division S9 League of Legends Global Finals champion skin theme?'},
   {'answer': 'GALIO',
    'options': [{'description': 'THRESH', 'label': '锤石', 'value': 'THRESH'},
     {'description': 'GALIO', 'label': '加里奥', 'value': 'GALIO'},
     {'description': 'VAYEN', 'label': '韦恩', 'value': 'VAYEN'}],
    'question': '以下哪个LOL英雄没有拥有S9冠军皮肤？\nWhich of the following LOL heroes does not have the S9 champion skin?'},
   {'answer': 'First',
    'options': [{'description': 'First', 'label': '第一', 'value': 'First'},
     {'description': 'second', 'label': '第二', 'value': 'second'},
     {'description': 'third', 'label': '第三', 'value': 'third'}],
    'question': '2021年S11英雄联盟全球总决赛开赛前夕，FPX电子竞技俱乐部排名全球战力榜第几？\nOn the eve of the 2021 S11 League of Legends global finals, where will the FPX e-sports club rank in the global power list?'},
   {'answer': 'G2',
    'options': [{'description': 'GEN', 'label': 'GEN', 'value': 'GEN'},
     {'description': 'G2', 'label': 'G2', 'value': 'G2'},
     {'description': 'MAD', 'label': 'MAD', 'value': 'MAD'}],
    'question': 'FPX电子竞技俱乐部和哪个外国电子竞技俱乐部是众所周知的好兄弟\nFPX eSports club and which foreign eSports club are well known good brothers'},
   {'answer': '5',
    'options': [{'description': '4', 'label': '四', 'value': '4'},
     {'description': '5', 'label': '五', 'value': '5'},
     {'description': '6', 'label': '六', 'value': '6'}],
    'question': 'FPX电子竞技俱乐部当前共有几个项目分部？\nHow many project divisions does the FPX e-sports club currently have?'},
   {'answer': '20M',
    'options': [{'description': '1M', 'label': '1M', 'value': '1M'},
     {'description': '8M', 'label': '8M', 'value': '8M'},
     {'description': '20M', 'label': '20M', 'value': '20M'}],
    'question': 'FPX电子竞技俱乐部在全球范围、各个平台共拥有多少粉丝？\nHow many fans does FPX e-sports club have globally and on various platforms?'},
   {'answer': '4billion',
    'options': [{'description': '2billion', 'label': '20亿', 'value': '2billion'},
     {'description': '3billion', 'label': '30亿', 'value': '3billion'},
     {'description': '4billion', 'label': '40亿', 'value': '4billion'}],
    'question': 'FPX电子竞技俱乐部在全球范围、各个平台共拥有多少话题阅读量（或者讨论量）？\nHow many topic readings (or discussions) does the FPX e-sports club have globally and on various platforms?'},
   {'answer': 'FNC',
    'options': [{'description': 'FNC', 'label': 'FNC', 'value': 'FNC'},
     {'description': 'G2', 'label': 'G2', 'value': 'G2'},
     {'description': 'TL', 'label': 'TL', 'value': 'TL'}],
    'question': 'FPX Valorant分部曾在VCT挑战者杯的比赛里打出了13:0惊为天人的比分，当时对阵的对手是谁?\nThe FPX Valorant division once scored an amazing 13-0 in the VCT Challenger Cup. Who was the opponent at that time?'},
   {'answer': 'March 27, 2022',
    'options': [{'description': 'March 7, 2022',
      'label': '2022年3月7日',
      'value': 'March 7, 2022'},
     {'description': 'March 17, 2022',
      'label': '2022年3月17日',
      'value': 'March 17, 2022'},
     {'description': 'March 27, 2022',
      'label': '2022年3月27日',
      'value': 'March 27, 2022'}],
    'question': 'FPX Valorant分部在哪一天获得了VCT EMEA CHALLENGERS的冠军？\nOn what day did the FPX Valorant division win the VCT EMEA CHALLENGERS?'},
   {'answer': 'FPX.Gimgoon',
    'options': [{'description': 'FPX.Cool',
      'label': 'FPX.Cool',
      'value': 'FPX.Cool'},
     {'description': 'FPX.Gimgoon',
      'label': 'FPX.Gimgoon',
      'value': 'FPX.Gimgoon'},
     {'description': 'FPX.Despa1r',
      'label': 'FPX.Despa1r',
      'value': 'FPX.Despa1r'}],
    'question': 'FPX电子竞技俱乐部哪位选手首位入驻FPX名人堂？\nWhich player from the FPX e-sports club was the first to be inducted into the FPX Hall of Fame?'},
   {'answer': 'May 8, 2022',
    'options': [{'description': 'March 8, 2022',
      'label': '2022年3月8日',
      'value': 'March 8, 2022'},
     {'description': 'April 8, 2022',
      'label': '2022年4月8日',
      'value': 'April 8, 2022'},
     {'description': 'May 8, 2022',
      'label': '2022年5月8日',
      'value': 'May 8, 2022'}],
    'question': 'FPX电子竞技俱乐部哪一天正式宣布将创造FPX元宇宙？\nWhen will the FPX esports club officially announce that it create the FPX metaverse?'},
   {'answer': 'FPX_META',
    'options': [{'description': 'FPX_NFTS',
      'label': 'FPX_NFTS',
      'value': 'FPX_NFTS'},
     {'description': 'FPX_META', 'label': 'FPX_META', 'value': 'FPX_META'},
     {'description': 'FPX_ESPORTS',
      'label': 'FPX_ESPORTS',
      'value': 'FPX_ESPORTS'}],
    'question': 'FPX电子竞技俱乐部元宇宙项目官方Twitter ID是？\nWhat is the official Twitter ID of FPX eSports Club Metaverse Project?'},
   {'answer': 'Phoenix',
    'options': [{'description': 'eagle', 'label': '老鹰', 'value': 'eagle'},
     {'description': 'Phoenix', 'label': '凤凰', 'value': 'Phoenix'},
     {'description': 'owl', 'label': '猫头鹰', 'value': 'owl'}],
    'question': 'FPX电子竞技俱乐部的吉祥物是？\nWhat is the mascot of the FPX eSports club?'},
   {'answer': 'Fly Phoenix Fly',
    'options': [{'description': 'Let’s go FPX',
      'label': 'Let’s go FPX',
      'value': 'Let’s go FPX'},
     {'description': 'Legends Never Die',
      'label': 'Legends Never Die',
      'value': 'Legends Never Die'},
     {'description': 'Fly Phoenix Fly',
      'label': 'Fly Phoenix Fly',
      'value': 'Fly Phoenix Fly'}],
    'question': '以下哪一句是FPX电子竞技俱乐部slogan？\nWhich of the following is the FPX esports club slogan?'},
   {'answer': '11',
    'options': [{'description': '10', 'label': '10', 'value': '10'},
     {'description': '11', 'label': '11', 'value': '11'},
     {'description': '12', 'label': '12', 'value': '12'}],
    'question': 'FPX电子竞技俱乐部共在几个国家举办过大型的线下粉丝活动？\nHow many countries has the FPX eSports club held large offline fan events?'},
   {'answer': 'Phoenix',
    'options': [{'description': 'Phoenix',
      'label': 'Phoenix',
      'value': 'Phoenix'},
     {'description': 'Legends Never Die',
      'label': 'Legends Never Die',
      'value': 'Legends Never Die'},
     {'description': 'Warriors', 'label': 'Warriors', 'value': 'Warriors'}],
    'question': "作为全球第一支与环球音乐合作发行的俱乐部主题曲，该作品名称是？\nAs the world's first club theme song released in cooperation with Universal Music, what is the name of this work?"},
   {'answer': 'MARVEL',
    'options': [{'description': 'FENDI', 'label': 'FENDI', 'value': 'FENDI'},
     {'description': 'NIKE', 'label': 'NIKE', 'value': 'NIKE'},
     {'description': 'MARVEL', 'label': 'MARVEL', 'value': 'MARVEL'}],
    'question': '2021年，FPX与哪家全球顶尖品牌合作针对电竞玩家推出一系列联名周边？\nIn 2021, which global top brand will FPX collaborate with to launch a series of joint merchandise for e-sports players?'},
   {'answer': 'Film Industry',
    'options': [{'description': 'Trendy lifestyle & top brand joint name',
      'label': '潮流生活方式&顶尖品牌联名',
      'value': 'Trendy lifestyle & top brand joint name'},
     {'description': 'Metaverse depth layout',
      'label': '元宇宙深度布局',
      'value': 'Metaverse depth layout'},
     {'description': 'Film Industry',
      'label': '电影产业',
      'value': 'Film Industry'}],
    'question': "以下哪条业务线不属于FPX电子竞技俱乐部的商业版图？\nWhich of the following lines of business is not part of FPX Esports Club's business landscape?"},
   {'answer': 'FunPlus',
    'options': [{'description': 'FunPlus',
      'label': 'FunPlus',
      'value': 'FunPlus'},
     {'description': 'FunPlay', 'label': 'FunPlay', 'value': 'FunPlay'},
     {'description': 'ForPassion',
      'label': 'ForPassion',
      'value': 'ForPassion'}],
    'question': '哪家世界级的互动娱乐集团创立了FPX电子竞技俱乐部？\nWhich world-class interactive entertainment group founded the FPX esports club?'},
   {'answer': 'Faith',
    'options': [{'description': 'Faith', 'label': 'Faith', 'value': 'Faith'},
     {'description': 'Fun', 'label': 'Fun', 'value': 'Fun'},
     {'description': 'Flame', 'label': 'Flame', 'value': 'Flame'}],
    'question': '通常我们解读FPX时，F代表？\nUsually when we interpret FPX, F stands for?'},
   {'answer': 'Passion',
    'options': [{'description': 'Possibility',
      'label': 'Possibility',
      'value': 'Possibility'},
     {'description': 'Peace', 'label': 'Peace', 'value': 'Peace'},
     {'description': 'Passion', 'label': 'Passion', 'value': 'Passion'}],
    'question': '通常我们解读FPX时，P代表？\nUsually when we interpret FPX, P stands for?'},
   {'answer': '5',
    'options': [{'description': '3', 'label': '三', 'value': '3'},
     {'description': '4', 'label': '四', 'value': '4'},
     {'description': '5', 'label': '五', 'value': '5'}],
    'question': "FPX全球顶级合作伙伴BMW的强者之盟（#UnitedInRivalry#）中共有包含FPX在内的几只全球顶级电竞战队？\nFPX's top global partner, BMW's League of Powers (#UnitedInRivalry#), how many world's top e-sports teams including FPX are included?"},
   {'answer': 'Watching Center',
    'options': [{'description': 'Talent Assessment Center',
      'label': '天赋测评中心',
      'value': 'Talent Assessment Center'},
     {'description': 'Data Analysis Center',
      'label': '数据分析中心',
      'value': 'Data Analysis Center'},
     {'description': 'Watching Center',
      'label': '观赛中心',
      'value': 'Watching Center'}],
    'question': "FPX在2022年度发布的高科技Esports Lab项目中不包含以下哪一部分内容？\nWhich of the following will not be included in FPX's 2022 release of the high-tech Esports Lab program?"},
   {'answer': 'Psychological Counseling Course',
    'options': [{'description': 'Esports Industry Education Course',
      'label': '电竞产业教育课程',
      'value': 'Esports Industry Education Course'},
     {'description': 'Psychological Counseling Course',
      'label': '心理咨询课程',
      'value': 'Psychological Counseling Course'},
     {'description': 'E-sports competition practical skills course',
      'label': '电竞比赛实操技能课程',
      'value': 'E-sports competition practical skills course'}],
    'question': '作为完善整个电竞生态的关键举措，FPX在2022年度发布的FPX Academy项目中，不包括以下哪部分内容？\nAs a key measure to improve the entire e-sports ecosystem, which of the following is not included in the FPX Academy project released by FPX in 2022?'}]

}